[Music]
[音乐]
hi my name is Vicente Romero I work at
嗨，我叫维森特·罗梅罗（Vicente Romero），我在
the job done at coracle and today I'm
在甲骨文做的工作，今天我
going to meet an introduction to Jeff
会见杰夫的介绍
three-two-three local burial syntax for
三二三本地埋葬语法
now the parameters in this section we
现在，本节中的参数
are going to talk about local variable
要谈论局部变量
syntax for landed parameters which is a
登陆参数的语法是
new feature included in Java SE 11
Java SE 11中包含的新功能
this feature is related to three
此功能与三个
official named local variable type
官方命名的局部变量类型
inference which has a broader goal as it
推论具有更广泛的目标
affected local variables which are in
受影响的局部变量
general more frequent than the
一般比
parameters this new feature were talking
这个新功能正在讨论的参数
about the employee changes to the Java
关于员工对Java所做的更改
language specification and to like Java
语言规范和喜欢Java
C and each shell local borlaug type
C和每个shell的本地Borlaug类型
inference extended type inference to the
推断扩展类型
corrections of local variables with
修正局部变量
initializers as shown in the provided
如所提供的初始化程序
example the compiler and infer the type
示例编译器并推断类型
of local variables with the from the
来自的局部变量
initializer without additional
初始化程序，无需附加
information from the user this leads to
来自用户的信息，这导致
less ceremony but keeps Java full static
较少的仪式，但保持Java完全静态
type safety others local variable syntax
类型安全其他局部变量语法
for nano parameters are in a nutshell
纳米参数概述
uniformity it aligns the syntax of the
一致性，它使
formal parameter declaration in an
形式参数声明
especially type lung expression with the
特别是肺部表达与
syntax of a local variable declaration
局部变量声明的语法
ensured the two declarations shown shown
确保显示的两个声明
here are allowed by the Java compiler
Java编译器允许在这里
and are considered equivalent as an
并被视为等同于
additional benefit now annotations can
注释现在可以带来更多好处
be applied to lambda
应用于lambda
formal without losing verb T as we can
正式而又不丢失动词T
see in this example there are some
看到在这个例子中有一些
restrictions to the use of the local
限制使用当地
variable think that for the parameters
变量认为对于参数
though it can only be used for the
尽管它只能用于
formal parameters of increasingly type
形式参数越来越多
lambda and is used for one for one
lambda，用于一对一
parameter in an expression it should be
表达式中的参数应为
used for roadman as a consequence the
因此用于守门员
following sample are considered legal by
以下样本被视为合法
the compiler there are some additional
编译器还有一些其他的
restrictions for example he was excited
限制，例如，他很兴奋
that should in order to maintain the
那应该是为了维持
brevity of the shorthand syntax the
速记语法的简短
following example is considered illegal
以下示例被视为非法
by the java language and compiler Oracle
由Java语言和编译器Oracle
is the steward of Java providing a large
是Java的管家
amount of development engineering found
找到的开发工程数量
in the Java platform and open Jenica
在Java平台中并打开Jenica
Oracle provides leading to a streaming
Oracle提供领先的流媒体
support for low cost easy to purchase
支持低成本易于购买
with simple pricing tiers and with that
具有简单的定价层级
thank you for watching
谢谢你的收看
[Music]
[音乐]